### Joseph Gudzak

Email: Gudzak6@yahoo.com • 732-343-4430 • New York

### **Profile**

Product leader with 6+ years of experience at startups and fortune 50 companies. Track record of building web user experiences in the Fintech and Adtech space that have impacted millions of customers. Currently focused on building tools to support internal teams that work with Comcast's demand side platform

# **Work Experience**

Comcast, New York NY

9/2022-Present

Product Manager, Beeswax

- Developed and executed product strategy for the application team, optimizing the demand side platform for 100+ enterprise clients
- Led the product discovery and development of new campaign tools that resulted in a 30% increase in customer efficiency
- Coordinated launch of product releases and webinar trainings across marketing, account management and sales teams, leading to a 5% increase in new user acquisitions

#### Voyager Digital, New York NY

5/2021-9/2022

Product Manager of Customer Experience

- Defined strategic vision and roadmap for the mobile app, collaborating with marketing, support, and leadership teams, contributing to a customer base growth to 2.5M users.
- Leveraged customer insights and analytics to drive growth campaigns, achieving a 10% increase in funded accounts
- Collaborated with product design and data teams on product discovery for new features through user interviews, support tickets, and competitive analysis, leading to a 15% increase in feature adoption.
- Engaged cross-functionally to communicate product requirements and dependencies, successfully driving key initiatives from conception to launch, resulting in a 20% faster time-to-market.

# Prudential Financial, Newark NJ

9/2018-5/2021

Associate Product Manager in the Customer Office

- Identified product opportunities for the Identity Management team to expands its product feature set which led to an increase of 50K users and additional \$400 AUM
- Collaborated with internal stakeholders to established a new onboarding tool to allow efficient set up of new messaging inquiries and improve efficiency by over 40%
- Partnered with engineering and data teams to identify user friction points in our account recovery process which led to an increase success rate of 25%
- Developed a new Alerts API that helped increase cost savings by 20% and deliver over 3 million communications annually through email, sms, and inbox

#### **EDUCATION**

Monmouth University, West Long Branch, New Jersey Bachelor of Science in Software Engineering

Graduated 5/2018

## SKILLS

Programming: Java, SQL, Python, HTML/CSS, Javascript

Technologies: Jira, Figma, Salesforce, Mixpanel, Tableau, Miro, Github, Postman, Invision, Adobe